Nguyen Khac Thanh

Contact

Nationality: Vietnamese Address: Hoai Duc District, Hanoi Date of Birth: April 1998 Phone number: 0968614342

Email: nguyenkhacthanh244@gmail.com

Blog: <u>nkthanh.dev</u>

About me

I studied Computer Science at the University of Engineering and Technology but I left the university since I didn't finish my program, so I never have a BA degree. I have been a software developer for 3 years.

I can communicate and read English documents. In my free time, I usually read Medium, review code on Github, learn new technology or improve my programming skills or write my blog.

I can use Linux and toolsets for development, apply basic data structures and algorithms to resolve problems (heap, link list, hash map, sort, and so on...). I use Python as the main programming language and I can improve the python program by using C/C++ or Cython. I need a good environment for self-development.

Work experiences

• 06-2019 – 02-2021: <u>Teko Vietnam</u>

Main responsibilities

- High-level design, write the document and implement product management module for the E-Commerce system
- Maintain and support infrastructure by using Kubernetes and related tools

Description

After 2 years, I applied to Teko Vietnam and I joined the catalog team. This is a product management system for the E-Commerce system. I have contributed to design product models and developed a microservice. My team has used Flask as the main framework. At this time, I improved skill programming and the high-level design system (data model, agile process, so on...). I also learned Docker and Kubernetes for development and deployment. By using utilities

(docker, kubectl, gcloud, scaffold, telepresence ...), I also understand the basic concepts and architecture of Kubernetes.

• 07-2017 – 06-2019: Revotech

Main responsibilities

- Design and develop the backend service for serving a machine learning system.
- Implement a clustering algorithm for oil prediction.
- Implement some machine learning algorithms, that are based on papers of researchers.

Description

In the first position, I was a backend developer for a machine learning system in the lab of the university. I and my team developed a backend system for serving machine learning models. I learned the basic software process, python, web service concept, and so on.

Skills

Programming language

- Python
- Javascript
- C/C++ (basic, support Python)
- Go (basic)

Frameworks

- The WSGI standards as Flask, Django, or ASGI standards as FastAPI,...
- The asynchronous library as asyncio, curio or gevent
- asyncpg, pymysql or SQLAlchemy
- Celery, Rq
- ExpressJS
- ReactJS (basic)

Database

- MySQL
- PostgresSQL (basic)

Testing

- Mock
- Unit testing with unittest, pytest
- API testing with Postman

Tools

- Linux
- Docker (for packaging), Kubernetes (for monitoring)
- OpenAPI documentation

Educations

• June 2019 - present

Learning Computer Science and Software development in Coursera and related platforms.

You can view my profile in <u>Coursera</u> or in <u>Freecodecamp</u>.

• Aug 2016 - June 2019

Studied Computer Communications and Networks at the University of Engineering and Technology.